question_data=[
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]

'''
For API quiz questions just remove the first dictionary.
URL -> https://opentdb.com/
'''

question_data_two=[{
    "type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"hard",
    "category":"Entertainment: Video Games",
    "question":"In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man&#039;s Tree.",
    "correct_answer":"True",
    "incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {
    "type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"History","question":"Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"3 members of 2 Live Crew were arrested for playing songs from their album, As Nasty As They Wanna Be, live.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The set of all algebraic numbers is countable.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Animals","question":"A bear does NOT defecate during hibernation. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"History","question":"The Cold War ended with Joseph Stalin&#039;s death.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]